So friends, if you want to invest your money in the market,
then join
Angel Broking right now because it
provides you with a good, reliable
service and opening an account is also
absolutely free of cost. So join Angel
Broking today. The account opening link is
in the description. Open your account today. On the
other hand, ICICI Lombard has
seen a good increase in profits. There has been an
increase of 80%. The
company has posted a profit of up to 350 crores.
Grocery moot has seen an increase of up to 50%.
Next Free has
seen a growth of 10%. Underwriting
loss has reduced to 193 crores. It is equivalent to 10 crores on a yearly
basis. It has been a strong quarter.
Turmeric has been seen coming from the company in the grocery moot, so
you have to keep that thing in mind. On the
other hand, Ambuja
Cement is performing well. There is an
expression of happiness in profitability. There is an
18th century in revenue, which you can see. The
revenue figure is at 3,993 crores. The
estimate of 1925 crores is Thaali Idli.  But
although a little pressure has been seen, the
figure of CO crore has come out and the last drop
of the center has been seen, the matchstick
liquid is 17.1 chapters, in fact, it is
of these lines, he will keep it in the city.